question_data = {
    "response_code":0,
    "results":
        [{
            "type":"boolean",
            "difficulty":"easy",
            "category":"General Knowledge",
            "question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
            "correct_answer":"False",
            "incorrect_answers":["True"]},

            {"type":"boolean",
             "difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
             "correct_answer":"False",
             "incorrect_answers":["True"]},

            {"type":"boolean",
             "difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"French is an official language in Canada.",
             "correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},

            {"type":"boolean",
             "difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
             "correct_answer":"True",
             "incorrect_answers":["False"]},

            {"type":"boolean",
             "difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
             "correct_answer":"True",
             "incorrect_answers":["False"]},

            {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
             "correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

            {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
             "correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

            {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True",
             "incorrect_answers":["False"]},

            {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge",
             "question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in "
                        "1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
             "correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},

            {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy",
             "category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Sun rises from the North.",
             "correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}
